documentshub.com 2018-03-25

# Privacy Policy | DocumentsHub.Com

## Your Privacy is Our Responsibility:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online website based information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We collect emails in comment forms but we do not publish and sale any information to third parties. We use supposed person names, business names and addresses for protection. If any post matches someone’s information than there is no need to worry about because all personal data is supposed and mentioned here in our privacy policy.

## Google Ad-sense:

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, documentshub.com access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## Collection of Personal Information:

When visiting www.documentshub.com address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administrator site webmaster tools, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement:

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy then you may contact us at saimajillani04@gmail.com.

## Documents Hub Consultants
